Douglas Southall Freeman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1900-1954 (Box 4-120)
  - 1945 (Box 59)
    - General Mortgage Corp.
    - Gerhartdt, C. H.
    - Gimbel Brothers
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Goddard, Calvin
    - Greene, Joseph I.
    - “Haa-Hal” miscellaneous (Box 62)
    - Habas, Ralph A.
    - Haig, Robert M.
    - “Ham-Hg” miscellaneous
    - Hamner, Annis R.
    - “He-Ht” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - “Hu-Hz” miscellaneous
    - Income tax
    - Insurance
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Jenkins, L. Howard
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous
    - Kane, R. Keith and Mrs.
    - King, E. J.
    - “Kl-Lz” miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Lynde, S. A.
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous
    - MacArthur, Douglas
    - Maddux, Parker S.
    - Mann, Dean Albert R.
    - Marshall, George C.
    - Martin, Roscoe C.
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McCain, J. R.
    - McCarthy, Frank
    - McCloy, John J.
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous
    - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Munn, James B.
    - “N” miscellaneous (Box 63)
    - Nevins, Allan
    - Nimitz, C. W.
    - “O” miscellaneous, 1944-1945
    - “Pa-Ph” miscellaneous
    - Patterson, Robert P.
    - Perkins, Maxwell E.
    - Peyton, Lawrence W. H.
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous
    - Pomfret, John E.
    - Price, Byron
    - “Q-Rn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Readers Digest
    - Richmond, University of
    - Rister, Carl Coke
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, A. Willisv
    - Rockefeller, John D. Jr.
    - “Sa-Sb” miscellaneous
    - Satterfield, Dave E.
    - “Sc-Sd” miscellaneous
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Sj” miscellaneous
    - Selby, John
    - Shotwell, James T.
    - “Sk-Ss” miscellaneous
    - Smith (general)
    - Smith, Mrs. Farley, 1943-1945
    - Smith, Walter Bedell
    - Southern Railway
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - Sully, Julia
    - Suter, Thomas L., 1944-1945
    - Szanto, L.
    - “T” miscellaneous (Box 64)
    - Tax receipts
    - Thomson, Peggy
    - “U-V” miscellaneous
    - Vassar College
    - Van Oot, B. H.
    - “Wa-Wd” miscellaneous
    - Wall, Jane Davis
    - Watson, Thomas J.
    - “We-Wh” miscellaneous
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - Whiting, Lawrence H.
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Wilkins, Raymond S.
    - Williams (general), 1944-1945
    - Williams, Ben Ames, 1944-1945
    - Willits, Joseph H., 1944-1945
    - Wilson (general)
    - Woodrum, Clifton A.
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
  - 1946 (Box 65)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - Adams, Theodore F.
    - ABC board
    - Ainsworth, W. L.
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters
    - Anderson (general)
    - Asbury, Samuel E.
    - Ashworth, Mrs. Osbourne O.
    - Ashworth memorial
    - Automobiles
    - Aydelotte, Frank
    - Ayer, Thomas P.
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Barton, Robert
    - Bemiss, Samuel Merrifield
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikopf, Jacob
    - Bird, Lloyd
    - Board, C. F.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Books
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Boyd, Julian P.
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous (Box 66)
    - Bridenbaugh, Carl
    - Bridges, J. Malcolm
    - British embassy
    - Brown (general)
    - Bryan, John Stewart
    - Bryan, Tennant
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Bucknell University
    - Byrd, Harry Flood.
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous
    - Campbell-Ewald Co.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carter, Spencer L.
    - Cary, John B.
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mary Tyler
    - Christian, Andrew D.
    - Citizens Association
    - Clarke, Morell
    - Clemen, Rudolf A.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous (Box 67)
    - Cockrell, Monroe F.
    - Community chests
    - Confederate Museum
    - Corson, John J.
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Crimmins, W. L.
    - Crouch, Kenneth E.
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Dabney, Virginius
    - Darden, C. W.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis, Jackson
    - Davis (general)
    - Dayton, Fred E.
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodds, Harold
    - Dodson, E. Griffith
    - Durkin, Joseph T.
    - “E” miscellaneous
    - Easley, James S.
    - Eckenrode, H. J.
    - Edwards, J. W.
    - Eggleston, J. D.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Elliott, Louis D.
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society
    - Evans (general)
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous, 1945-1946
    - Fierabend, Charlotte Wise
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous (Box 68)
    - Forrestal, James V.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, Hamner
    - Freeman, James Douglas
      - General
      - Insurance
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Frank P.
    - Garden, 1943-1946
    - Garnett, W. E.
    - General Education Board
    - Gillette, Charles F.
    - Gimbel Brothers
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Goddard, Calvin
    - Goodloe, Henry L.
    - Graham, Mrs. J. George M.
    - Grime, A. T.
    - Gruenther, A. M.
    - Guerry, Alexander
    - “Haa-Hal” miscellaneous (Box 69)
    - Habas, Ralph A.
    - Halifax, Earl of
    - Hall, Wilmer L.
    - “Ham-Hd” miscellaneous
    - Hamner, Annis
    - Hancock, Gordon B.
    - Harris, H. Hiter
    - Harrison, miscellaneus
    - “He-Hn” miscellaneous
    - Herbert, W. C.
    - “Ho-Ht” miscellaneous
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - Hotels
    - “Hu-I” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Insurance
    - Ivey, James H.
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Johnson (general)
    - Johnston, J. Amber
    - Jones (general)
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous (Box 70)
    - Kane, R. Keith and Mrs.
    - Kilbourne, Charles E.
    - “Kl-Ln” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Lewis, B. R.
    - Library of Congress Committee
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - Lovenstein, Meno
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous
    - Macy, George
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Mann, Albert R.
    - Marshall, R. J.
    - Martin, miscellaneus
    - Massie, Wood and West
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McAdams, Thomas B.
    - McCain, J. R.
    - McLoy, John J.
    - McCurdy, Charles P.
    - McNeil, Robert H.
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous (Box 71)
    - Melius, Don C.
    - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - Miller, miscellaneous
    - Miller, Francis Pickens
    - Mitchell, S. C.
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Modlin, George M.
    - Munn, James B.
    - “N” miscellaneous
    - Nevins, Allan
    - Newcomen dinner
    - News Leader Current Events Club
    - Nimitz, Chester W.
    - Norris, Ernest
    - “O-Ph” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Parker (general)
    - Parkinson, Thomas I.
    - Patterson, Robert P.
    - Perkinson, Hazel
    - Peyton, L. W. H.
    - Phi Beta Kappa
    - Phillips, Charles H.
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous (Box 72)
    - Pittsburgh, University of
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America
    - Pomfret, John E.
    - Powell (general)
    - Prentice, Colgate S.
    - President's Commission on Higher Education
    - Price, Byron
    - Princeton battlefield
    - “Q-Rn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Receipts
    - Rhoads, Webster S.
    - Rhodes Scholarship
    - Richmond, University of, (2 folders)
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, Walter S.
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Rockefeller, John D. and III
    - “Sa-Sb” miscellaneous (Box 73)
    - Sanger, William T.
    - Saville, Allen J.
    - “Sc-Sd” miscellaneous
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Sj” miscellaneous
    - Shotwell, James T.
    - “Sk-Ss” miscellaneous
    - Sledd, Hunter C.
    - Smith (general)
    - Smith, Ellen H.
    - Smith, Walter Bedell
    - Solari's
    - Southern Railway
    - Southern Railway luncheon
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - Stettinius, Edward R.
    - Stewart, Annie C.
    - Sully, Julia
    - Swiss Colony
    - Sydnor, A. D.
    - “T” miscellaneous
    - Talbot, Edmond E.
    - Tax receipts
    - Taylor (general)
    - Terminix Co.
    - Torrence, William Clayton
    - Trigg, Emma Gray
    - Tuck, William M.
    - Turner (general)
    - “U-V” miscellaneous (Box 74)
    - Underwood, R. B.
    - Valentine Museum
    - Vandiver, Frank
    - Virginia Historical Society
    - “Wa-Wd” miscellaneous
    - Walker, J. Carter
    - Wall, Jane Davis
    - Washington, George
    - “We-Wh” miscellaneous
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - Westbourne
    - White (general)
    - Whitlock, E. S.
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Wicker, John J.
    - Willkie Awards
    - Wilkinson, Cecil J.
    - Williams, General
    - Williams, Ben Ames
    - Williams, Fred, case
    - Wilson (general)
    - Wise, John Dana
    - Woodbridge, Henley C.
    - Woodrum, Clifton A.
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
    - Yale University, 1946
  - 1947 (Box 75)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - ABC Board
    - Addresses (general)
    - Ainsworth, W. L.
    - Allen (general)
    - American, Academy of Arts and Letters
    - American, Aid to France
    - American, Philosophical Society
    - Anderson (general)
    - Antiquarian, society
    - Ashwoth, O. O. and family
    - Automobile registration
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Battle, Abbey (information)
    - Bemiss, Samuel M.
    - “Bi-Bg” miscellaneous
    - Billikoph, Jacob
    - Binns, Walter Pope
    - Board, C. F.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Bolte, Charles L.
    - Books (general)
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Boyd, Julian P.
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous (Box 76)
    - Bridenbaugh, Carl
    - Bridges, J. Malcolm
    - Brown (general)
    - Bruce, George S.
    - Bryan, David T.
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Budget Bureau, U.S.
    - Byrd, Harry S.
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous
    - Cain, Benjamin B.
    - California, University of
    - Campbellk, Ewald
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carter, Spencer L.
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mrs.
    - Chicago, University of
    - Church, Randolph W.
    - Churchill, Winston
    - Christian, Ellen H.
    - Citizens Association
    - Clemen, Rudolf A.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Cockrell, Monroe F.
    - Commager, Henry Steele.
    - Community chests
    - Collier's Award
    - Confederate Museum
    - Corson, John J.
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous (Box 77)
    - Cutchins, John A.
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Daniloff, Gladys Taylor
    - Darden, Colgate W.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis, Jackson
    - Davis (general)
    - DeLaBarre, Cecil F.
    - Derwent property
    - Diggs and Beadles
    - Diggs, Gaius
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodson, E. Griffith
    - Dodds, Harold
    - Durkin, J. T.
    - “E” miscellaneous
    - Easley, James S.
    - Edwards, Horace H.
    - Edwards, J. W.
    - Eddleman, C. D.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Emmons, Delos C.
    - Equitable Life
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous
    - First and Merchants Bank
    - Firtchett, Otis
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous (Box 78)
    - Forrestal, James V.
    - Fosdick, Raymond D.
    - Food
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Annie B.
    - Freeman, Hamner G.
    - Freeman, James D.
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Francis P.
    - Garnett, W. E.
    - Gary, J. Vaughn
    - General Education Board
    - Gillette, Charles F.
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Green (general)
    - Greenfield, Kent Roberts
    - Gruenther, Alfred H.
    - Guerry, Alexander
    - Guy, Amy A.
    - Hall of Fame
    - “Haa-Hd” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - Halsey, William F.
    - Hamner, Annis
    - Hancock, Gordon B.
    - Harris, H. Hiter
    - Harrison (general)
    - “He-Hn” miscellaneous
    - Hendricks, Sam
    - Henry, Patrick, Memorial Association
    - Hill, Henry H.
    - “Ho-Ht” miscellaneous
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - Hotels
    - “Hu-Hz” miscellaneous
    - “I” miscellaneous (Box 80)
    - Income tax
    - Insurance
    - Insurance (N. Y. Life)
    - Ivy, James Houston
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Johnston, Dudley R.
    - Johnston, James Ambler
    - Jones (general)
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous
    - Kane, Keith and Mrs.
    - King, Ernest J.
    - “Kl-Ld” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Lee's Lieutenants
      - Contract
      - Presentation copies
      - Errors
    - “Le-Ln” miscellaneous
    - Library of Congress
    - Lincoln Book Shop
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - Lyne, Cassie M.
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous (Box 81)
    - MacArthur, Douglas
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Martin (general)
    - Marx, Joseph L.
    - Massie, Wood and West
    - McCown, Albert S.
    - McAdams, Thomas B.
    - McNeil, Robert H.
    - “Mc-Mn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Mealey, Emmett
    - Meade, Edward B.
    - Melius, Donald C.
    - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - Miller, Harold F., family
    - Miller (general)
    - Mitchell, S C.
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Modlin, George M.
    - Morison, Samuel E.
    - Morristown, N.J., trip
    - Munn, James B.
    - “N” miscellaneous
    - Nelson, Robert F.
    - News Leader Current Events Club
    - Norris, Ernest
    - “O” miscellaneous
    - “Pa-Ph” miscellaneous (Box 82)
    - Parkinson, Thomas I.
    - Patterson, Robert J.
    - Patton, Mrs. George C.
    - Peed, Garland Powell
    - Peyton, Lawrence W. H.
    - Phi Beta Kappa
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous
    - Pittsburg, University of
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America
    - Pomfret, John E.
    - Powell, Louis F., Jr.
    - President's Commission on Higher Education
    - Princeton
    - “O-Rn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Ratcliffe, Clyde, Jr.
    - Receipts
    - Rhoads, Webster
    - Rhodes Scholarship
    - Richmond, University of
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Robertson, Wolfer S.
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Ruddock family
    - “Sa-Sd” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 83)
    - Scribner, Charles
    - Schmidt and Wilson
    - “Se-Ss” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Smith (general)
    - Southern Railway, (2 folders)
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - State, Department
    - Sully, Julia
    - Suter, Thomas L.
    - Suzuki, J.
    - Swiss Colony
    - Sydnor, D. H.
    - Szanto, Louis
    - “T” miscellaneous
    - Tuck, William M.
    - Tax receipts
    - Taylor (general)
    - Trigg, William R.
    - “U-V” miscellaneous (Box 84)
    - Valentine Museum
    - Vandiver, Frank
    - Virginia Historical Society
    - “Wa-Wd” miscellaneous
    - Wall, Jane Davis
    - Wallet, lost
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - “We-Wh” miscellaneous
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Wellford, B. Randolph
    - Westbourne
    - White, Joseph F.
    - Whitehill, Walter Muir
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Wicker, John J.
    - Williams, Ben Ames
    - Williams (general)
    - Wilkie Awards
    - Wilson (general)
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
  - 1948 (Box 85)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - ABC Board
    - Academy of Arts and Letters
    - Adams, Dr. Theodore F.
    - Adams (general)
    - Alley, C. Willard
    - American Philosophical Society
    - Ainsworth, Admiral W. L.
    - Anderson (general)
    - Arnold, Remmie L.
    - Ashworth family
    - Automobiles
    - Aydelotte, Frank
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Bemiss, Sam M.
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikoph, Jacob
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Board, C. F.
    - Books
    - Boushall, Thomas
    - Boyd, Julian
    - Bracken, Brendan
    - Bremner, W. D.
    - Brydon, G. MacLaren
    - Bridenbaugh
    - Bridges, J. Malcolm
    - Brown (general)
    - “Br-Bz” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Byrd, Harry Flood.
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous (Box 86)
    - Cabell, Royal E.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carter, Robert
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mrs.
    - Christian, R. E.
    - Church, R. W.
    - Clemen, Rudolph A.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Cochran, H. G.
    - Codd, L. A.
    - Cole, Charles F.
    - Colde, Ezra D.
    - Collier's Awards
    - Columbia University (Bancroft Awards)
    - Community chests
    - Confederate Museum
    - Cook, Roy Bird
    - Cook and Son Co.
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Cuyler, T. Cruger
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous (Box 87)
    - Darden, C. W. ,Jr.
    - Darneille, R. J.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis (general)
    - Dellinger, James L.
    - Devers, Jacob L.
    - “Do-E” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Eckenrode, H. J.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Eddy, M. S.
    - Edwards, Horace H.
    - Edwards, J. W.
    - Emerson, Barbara
    - Evans (general)
    - Equitable Life Co.
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous
    - Fairchild, Muir S.
    - First and Merchants Bank
    - Fitchett, W. Otis
    - Fleet, Elizabeth M.
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous
    - Fox, William A.
    - Freeman, Allen W. (Box 88)
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, James Douglas
    - Freeman, W. B.
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Francis P.
    - Garfield, Abram
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Glasgow, Arthur G.
    - Goddard, Calvin H.
    - Green (general)
    - Greenfield, Kent Roberts
    - Greentree, Irving S.
    - Gregg, Alan
    - Guerry, Alexander
    - “Haa-Hd” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Hamner, Annis R.
    - Hancock, Gordon B.
    - Harris, H. Hiter
    - Harrison (general)
    - “He-Hn” miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - Hendricks, Sam
    - Hewlett, Martha
    - “Ho-Ht” miscellaneous
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - Hotels
    - “Hu-I” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Institute of Early American History
    - Insurance
    - Ivey, James H.
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Johnson (general)
    - Johns Hopkins University
    - Johnston, Dudley R.
    - Johnston, J. Ambler
    - Jones (general)
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous (Box 90)
    - Kane, Keith and Mrs.
    - Kemp, Verbon E.
    - Kelley, N. W.
    - “Kl-Ln” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Lee Errors
    - Lee-Jackson monument
    - Library of Congress
    - Lincoln Bookstore
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - Lovenstein, Meno
    - Lucas, R. D.
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Marshall, Robert J.
    - Martin (general)
    - May, Irving
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McAdams, Thomas B.
    - McGown, Albert S.
    - McNeil, Robert H.
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous (Box 91)
    - Mealy, Emmett
    - Melius, Don C.
    - Meyer, Agnes
    - Miller, Francis P.
    - Miller (general)
    - Mitchell, George S.
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Morison, Samuel E.
    - Modlin, George M.
    - Moore, Marjorie
    - Moore, Marjorie E.
    - “N” miscellaneous
    - Negus, Sidney S.
    - Nelson, Robert F.
    - Nevins, Allan
    - News Leader Current Events Club
    - Norris, Ernest
    - Norfleet, Fillmore and Mrs.
    - “O-Ph” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Parker (general)
    - Peed, Garland Powell
    - Perkison, Hazel
    - Phi Gamma Delta
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous
    - Pollard, Warren R.
    - Pomfret, John Edwin
    - Powell, Lewis F.
    - Princeton University
    - “Q-Rn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Receipts
    - Reservations
    - Rhoads, Webster
    - Rhodes Scholarship
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Roper, Wilfred A.
    - Robertson, Archie G.
    - Rockefeller family
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Ryland, S. Peachy
    - “Sa-Sb” miscellaneous (Box 93)
    - Safron, Max
    - “Sc-Sd” miscellaneous
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Sj” miscellaneous
    - Shepherd, Lemuel C.
    - Sigma Delta Chi
    - Shotwell, James T.
    - “Sk-Ss” miscellaneous
    - Smith (general)
    - Southern Railway
    - Southern Railway luncheon
    - Spruance, Raymond A.
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - Straver, Joseph R.
    - Sully, Julia
    - “T” miscellaneous
    - Taylor (general)
    - Tax receipts
    - Tuck, William M.
    - “U-V” miscellaneous (Box 94)
    - Valentine Museum
    - Vandiver, Frank
    - Van Doren, Carl
    - Virginia Historical Society
    - Von Boetticher, General Friedrich
    - “Wa-Wd” miscellaneous
    - Walker (general)
    - Washington and Lee University
    - “We-Wh” miscellaneous
    - Weddell, Mrs. Alexander
    - Westbourne
    - White (general)
    - Whitehill, Walter Muir
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Williams (general)
    - Williamson, Betty
    - Willkie Awards
    - Wilson (general)
    - Wines
    - Woodlawn Public Foundation
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
  - 1949 (Box 95)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - ABC Board
    - Academy Arts and Letters
    - Allen (general)
    - American Association of Junior Colleges
    - Anderson (general)
    - Anderson, Mrs. Charles M.
    - Arnold, Remmie L.
    - Ashworth, O. O.
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Bancroft Award
    - Barnard, Chester
    - Beary, D. B.
    - Bemiss, Samuel M.
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikoph, Jacob
    - Books
    - Boothe, Armisted L.
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Boyd, Julian
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous
    - Bradley, Omar N.
    - Brown (general)
    - Bryant, D. Tennant
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Burlingham, Charles C.
    - Burress, Withers A.
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous (Box 96)
    - Carpenter, H. Beach
    - Carter, Louise
    - Carter, Robert H.
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Cheek family
    - Church, Randolph W.
    - Churchill, Winston
    - Clinchy, Everett R.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Cockrell, Monroe F.
    - Codd, L. A.
    - Collier's Awards
    - Confederate material
    - Cook, Roy Bird
    - Corson, John J.
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Cuyler, Cruger
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis (general)
    - Devers, Jacob L.
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodds, Harold
    - Dodson, Griffith
    - Driscoll, John
    - Dunne, D. M.
    - “E” miscellaneous
    - Easley, James S.
    - Eddy, Manton S.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Equitable Life Insurance Society
    - Evans (general)
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous (Box 97)
    - Finney, Eben D.
    - Fitchett, W. Otis
    - Fitzroy, Herbert W. K.
    - Florida University Libraries
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous
    - Food
    - Fosdick, Raymond B.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, finances
    - Freeman, James D.
    - Fuller, Frank
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - General Education Board
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Glasgow, Arthur G.
    - Green (general)
    - Greenfield, Kent R.
    - Gruening, Ernest
    - “Haa-Hal” miscellaneous
    - Hall of Fame, New York University
    - “Ham-Hay” miscellaneous
    - Hamner, Annis R.
    - Harvard University
    - Haydn, Hiram
    - “He-Hn” miscellaneous
    - Henry, Patrick Memorial Foundation
    - Hill, Harry W.
    - “Ho-Ht” miscellaneous
    - Holloway, J. L.
    - Horn, Stanley F.
    - Hotels
    - “Hu-Hz” miscellaneous
    - Huntington Library
    - Hurt, John
    - “I” miscellaneous
    - Inquiries
    - Insurance
    - Ivey, James Houston
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Jackson, Stuart W.
    - Johnston, J. Ambler
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous (Box 98)
    - Kane, R. Keith and Mrs.
    - Kemp, Verbon E.
    - Kentucky, University of
    - King, W. Stirling
    - “Kl-Ld” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - La Forge, Lawrence
    - “Le-Ln” miscellaneous
    - Lemmon, E. Travis
    - Life and Time Publishers
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - Lovenstein, Meno
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Manley, S. V.
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - Marshall, George C.
    - McAdams, Thomas B.
    - McCann, Robert C.
    - McCown, Albert S.
    - McGaw, E. J.
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous
    - Meade, Robert D.
    - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - Miller (general)
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Modlin, George M.
    - Morison, Samuel Eliot
    - Muller, Walter J.
    - “N” miscellaneous
    - News Leader
    - News Leader Current Events Club
    - New York Times
    - Norris, Ernest
    - “O” miscellaneous
    - Office expenses
    - “Pa-Pz” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Pilgrimages
    - Pinckney, Thomas
    - Planned Parenthood of America
    - Poe Foundation